bunited.com 2019-05-03

# None

bUnited knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. We appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly.

This Privacy Policy explains how bUnited, Inc. ("bUnited", "we" "us" and "our" in this Statement) uses data that we collect at the site and applies to all who use our website - www.bUnited.com ("Site").

Personal data (usually referred to just as "data" below) will only be processed by us to the extent necessary and for the purpose of providing a functional and user-friendly website, including its contents, and the services offered there.

Per Art. 4 No. 1 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679, i.e. the General Data Protection Regulation (hereinafter referred to as the "GDPR"), "processing" refers to any operation or set of operations such as collection, recording, organization, structuring, storage, adaptation, alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination, or otherwise making available, alignment, or combination, restriction, erasure, or destruction performed on personal data, whether by automated means or not.

The following privacy policy is intended to inform you in particular about the type, scope, purpose, duration, and legal basis for the processing of such data either under our own control or in conjunction with others. We also inform you below about the third-party components we use to optimize our website and improve the user experience which may result in said third parties also processing data they collect and control.

Our privacy policy is structured as follows:

I. Information about us as controllers of your data

II. The rights of users and data subjects

III. Information about the data processing

IV. Other

## **I. Information about us as controllers of your data**

The party responsible for this website (the "controller") for purposes of data protection law is:

bUnited Inc. 

2995 Woodside Road #400-551

Woodside, CA 94062  
USA

Telephone: +1 (800) 320-9434

Email: privacy@bUnited.com

The controller's data protection officer for European Union is:

Melody Sinclair-Brooks 

## **II. The rights of users and data subjects**

With regard to the data processing to be described in more detail below, users and data subjects have the right

  * to confirmation of whether data concerning them is being processed, information about the data being processed, further information about the nature of the data processing, and copies of the data (cf. also Art. 15 GDPR);

  * to correct or complete incorrect or incomplete data (cf. also Art. 16 GDPR);

  * to the immediate deletion of data concerning them (cf. also Art. 17 DSGVO), or, alternatively, if further processing is necessary as stipulated in Art. 17 Para. 3 GDPR, to restrict said processing per Art. 18 GDPR;

  * to receive copies of the data concerning them and/or provided by them and to have the same transmitted to other providers/controllers (cf. also Art. 20 GDPR);

  * to file complaints with the supervisory authority if they believe that data concerning them is being processed by the controller in breach of data protection provisions (see also Art. 77 GDPR).

In addition, the controller is obliged to inform all recipients to whom it discloses data of any such corrections, deletions, or restrictions placed on processing the same per Art. 16, 17 Para. 1, 18 GDPR. However, this obligation does not apply if such notification is impossible or involves a disproportionate effort. Nevertheless, users have a right to information about these recipients.

**Likewise, under Art. 21 GDPR, users and data subjects have the right to object to the controller's future processing of their data pursuant to Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. In particular, an objection to data processing for the purpose of direct advertising is permissible.**

## **III. Information about the data processing**

Your data processed when using our website will be deleted or blocked as soon as the purpose for its storage ceases to apply, provided the deletion of the same is not in breach of any statutory storage obligations or unless otherwise stipulated below.

#### **Server data**

For technical reasons, the following data sent by your internet browser to us or to our server provider will be collected, especially to ensure a secure and stable website: These server log files record the type and version of your browser, operating system, the website from which you came (referrer URL), the webpages on our site visited, the date and time of your visit, as well as the IP address from which you visited our site.

The data thus collected will be temporarily stored, but not in association with any other of your data.

The basis for this storage is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in the improvement, stability, functionality, and security of our website.

The data will be deleted within no more than seven days, unless continued storage is required for evidentiary purposes. In which case, all or part of the data will be excluded from deletion until the investigation of the relevant incident is finally resolved.

#### **Cookies**

##### **a) Session cookies**

We use cookies on our website. Cookies are small text files or other storage technologies stored on your computer by your browser. These cookies process certain specific information about you, such as your browser, location data, or IP address.  

This processing makes our website more user-friendly, efficient, and secure, allowing us, for example, to display our website in different languages.

The legal basis for such processing is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b) GDPR, insofar as these cookies are used to collect data to initiate or process contractual relationships.

If the processing does not serve to initiate or process a contract, our legitimate interest lies in improving the functionality of our website. The legal basis is then Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR.

When you close your browser, these session cookies are deleted.

##### **b) Third-party cookies**

If necessary, our website may also use cookies from companies with whom we cooperate for the purpose of advertising, analyzing, or improving the features of our website.

Please refer to the following information for details, in particular for the legal basis and purpose of such third-party collection and processing of data collected through cookies.

##### **c) Disabling cookies**

You can refuse the use of cookies by changing the settings on your browser. Likewise, you can use the browser to delete cookies that have already been stored. However, the steps and measures required vary, depending on the browser you use. If you have any questions, please use the help function or consult the documentation for your browser or contact its maker for support. Browser settings cannot prevent so-called flash cookies from being set. Instead, you will need to change the setting of your Flash player. The steps and measures required for this also depend on the Flash player you are using. If you have any questions, please use the help function or consult the documentation for your Flash player or contact its maker for support.

If you prevent or restrict the installation of cookies, not all of the functions on our site may be fully usable.

#### **Member account/registration**

If you create a member account with us via our website, we will use the data you entered during registration (e.g. NAME, LAST NAME, EMAIL-ADDRESS, LAND) exclusively for services leading up to entering some other contractual relationship with partner companies and to provide member care (e.g. to provide you with an overview of your previous activities). We also store your IP address and the date and time of your registration. This data will not be transferred to third parties.

During the registration process, your consent will be obtained for this processing of your data, with reference made to this privacy policy. The data collected by us will be used exclusively to provide your member account. 

If you give your consent to this processing, Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a) GDPR is the legal basis for this processing.

If the opening of the member account is also intended to lead to the initiation of a contractual relationship with us or to fulfill an existing contract with us, the legal basis for this processing is also Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b) GDPR.

You may revoke your prior consent to the processing of your personal data at any time under Art. 7 Para. 3 GDPR with future effect. All you have to do is inform us that you are revoking your consent.

The data previously collected will then be deleted as soon as processing is no longer necessary. However, we must observe any retention periods required under tax and commercial law.

#### **Newsletter**

If you register for our free newsletter, the data requested from you for this purpose, i.e. your email address and, optionally, your name and address, will be sent to us. We also store the IP address of your computer and the date and time of your registration. During the registration process, we will obtain your consent to receive this newsletter and the type of content it will offer, with reference made to this privacy policy. The data collected will be used exclusively to send the newsletter and will not be passed on to third parties.

The legal basis for this is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a) GDPR.

You may revoke your prior consent to receive this newsletter under Art. 7 Para. 3 GDPR with future effect. All you have to do is inform us that you are revoking your consent or click on the unsubscribe link contained in each newsletter.

#### **Contact**

If you contact us via email or the contact form, the data you provide will be used for the purpose of processing your request. We must have this data in order to process and answer your inquiry; otherwise we will not be able to answer it in full or at all.

The legal basis for this data processing is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b) GDPR.

Your data will be deleted once we have fully answered your inquiry and there is no further legal obligation to store your data, such as if an order or contract resulted therefrom.

#### **Google Analytics**

We use Google Analytics on our website. This is a web analytics service provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 (hereinafter: Google).

Through certification according to the EU-US Privacy Shield

[https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active)

Google guarantees that it will follow the EU's data protection regulations when processing data in the United States.

The Google Analytics service is used to analyze how our website is used. The legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in the analysis, optimization, and economic operation of our site.

Usage and user-related information, such as IP address, place, time, or frequency of your visits to our website will be transmitted to a Google server in the United States and stored there. However, we use Google Analytics with the so-called anonymization function, whereby Google truncates the IP address within the EU or the EEA before it is transmitted to the US.

The data collected in this way is in turn used by Google to provide us with an evaluation of visits to our website and what visitors do once there. This data can also be used to provide other services related to the use of our website and of the internet in general.

Google states that it will not connect your IP address to other data. In addition, Google provides further information with regard to its data protection practices at

including options you can exercise to prevent such use of your data.

In addition, Google offers an opt-out add-on at

in addition with further information. This add-on can be installed on the most popular browsers and offers you further control over the data that Google collects when you visit our website. The add-on informs Google Analytics' JavaScript (ga.js) that no information about the website visit should be transmitted to Google Analytics. However, this does not prevent information from being transmitted to us or to other web analytics services we may use as detailed herein.

#### **Google Fonts**

Our website uses Google Fonts to display external fonts. This is a service provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 (hereinafter: Google).

Through certification according to the EU-US Privacy Shield

[https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active)

Google guarantees that it will follow the EU's data protection regulations when processing data in the United States.

To enable the display of certain fonts on our website, a connection to the Google server in the USA is established whenever our website is accessed.

The legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in the optimization and economic operation of our site.

When you access our site, a connection to Google is established from which Google can identify the site from which your request has been sent and to which IP address the fonts are being transmitted for display.

Google offers detailed information at

<https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated>

<https://policies.google.com/privacy>

in particular on options for preventing the use of data.

#### **Facebook plug-in**

Our website uses the plug-in of the Facebook social network. Facebook.com is a service provided by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. In the EU, this service is also operated by Facebook Ireland Limited, 4 Grand Canal Square, Dublin 2, Ireland, hereinafter both referred to as "Facebook."

Through certification according to the EU-US Privacy Shield

[https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000GnywAAC&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000GnywAAC&status=Active)

Facebook guarantees that it will follow the EU's data protection regulations when processing data in the United States.

The legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in improving the quality of our website.

Further information about the possible plug-ins and their respective functions is available from Facebook at

<https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/>

If the plug-in is stored on one of the pages you visit on our website, your browser will download an icon for the plug-in from Facebook's servers in the USA. For technical reasons, it is necessary for Facebook to process your IP address. In addition, the date and time of your visit to our website will also be recorded.

If you are logged in to Facebook while visiting one of our plugged-in websites, the information collected by the plug-in from your specific visit will be recognized by Facebook. The information collected may then be assigned to your personal account at Facebook. If, for example, you use the Facebook Like button, this information will be stored in your Facebook account and published on the Facebook platform. If you want to prevent this, you must either log out of Facebook before visiting our website or use an add-on for your browser to prevent the Facebook plug-in from loading.

Further information about the collection and use of data as well as your rights and protection options in Facebook's privacy policy found at

<https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>

#### **YouTube**

We use YouTube on our website. This is a video portal operated by YouTube LLC, 901 Cherry Ave, 94066 San Bruno, CA, USA, hereinafter referred to as "YouTube".

YouTube is a subsidiary of Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 USA, hereinafter referred to as "Google".

Through certification according to the EU-US Privacy Shield

[https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active)

Google and its subsidiary YouTube guarantee that they will follow the EU's data protection regulations when processing data in the United States.

We use YouTube in its advanced privacy mode to show you videos. The legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in improving the quality of our website. According to YouTube, the advanced privacy mode means that the data specified below will only be transmitted to the YouTube server if you actually start a video.

Without this mode, a connection to the YouTube server in the USA will be established as soon as you access any of our webpages on which a YouTube video is embedded.

This connection is required in order to be able to display the respective video on our website within your browser. YouTube will record and process at a minimum your IP address, the date and time the video was displayed, as well as the website you visited. In addition, a connection to the DoubleClick advertising network of Google is established.

If you are logged in to YouTube when you access our site, YouTube will assign the connection information to your YouTube account. To prevent this, you must either log out of YouTube before visiting our site or make the appropriate settings in your YouTube account.

For the purpose of functionality and analysis of usage behavior, YouTube permanently stores cookies on your device via your browser. If you do not agree to this processing, you have the option of preventing the installation of cookies by making the appropriate settings in your browser. Further details can be found in the section about cookies above.

Further information about the collection and use of data as well as your rights and protection options in Google's privacy policy found at

<https://policies.google.com/privacy>

#### **Vimeo**

We use Vimeo to display videos on our website. This is a service of Vimeo, LLC, 555 West 18th Street, New York, New York 10011, USA, hereinafter referred to as "Vimeo."

Some of the user data is processed on Vimeo servers in the USA. Through certification according to the EU-US Privacy Shield

[(https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt00000008V77AAE&status=Active)](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt00000008V77AAE&status=Active)

Vimeo guarantees that it will follow the EU's data protection regulations when processing data in the United States.

The legal basis for collecting and processing this information is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in improving the quality of our website.

When you access a page on our website that has Vimeo embedded in it, a connection to Vimeo's servers in the USA is established. For technical reasons, it is necessary for Vimeo to process your IP address. In addition, the date and time of your visit to our website will also be recorded.

If you are logged into Vimeo while visiting one of our webpages containing a Vimeo video, Vimeo will associate information about your interaction with our site to your Vimeo account. If you wish to prevent this, you must either log out of Vimeo before visiting our website or configure your Vimeo user account accordingly.

For the purpose of functionality and usage analysis, Vimeo uses Google Analytics. Google Analytics stores cookies on your terminal device via your browser and transmits information about the use of those websites in which a Vimeo video is embedded to Google. It is possible that Google will process this information in the USA.

If you do not agree to this processing, you have the option of preventing the installation of cookies by making the appropriate settings in your browser. Further details can be found in the section about cookies above.

The legal basis for collecting and processing this information is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in improving the quality of our website and in Vimeo's legitimate interest in statistically analyzing user behavior for optimization and marketing purposes.

Vimeo offers further information about its data collection and processing as well your rights and your options for protecting your privacy at this link:

<http://vimeo.com/privacy>.

#### **MailChimp - Newsletter**

We offer you the opportunity to register for our free newsletter via our website.

We use MailChimp, a service of The Rocket Science Group, LLC, 512 Means Street, Suite 404, Atlanta, GA 30318, USA, hereinafter referred to as "The Rocket Science Group".

Through certification according to the EU-US Privacy Shield

[https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000TO6hAAG&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000TO6hAAG&status=Active)

the Rocket Science Group guarantees that it will follow the EU's data protection regulations when processing data in the United States. In addition, the Rocket Science Group offers further information about its data protection practices at

<http://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/>

If you register for our free newsletter, the data requested from you for this purpose, i.e. your email address and, optionally, your name and address, will be processed by The Rocket Science Group. In addition, your IP address and the date and time of your registration will be saved. During the registration process, your consent to receive this newsletter will be obtained together with a concrete description of the type of content it will offer and reference made to this privacy policy.

The newsletter then sent out by The Rocket Science Group will also contain a tracking pixel called a web beacon. This pixel helps us evaluate whether and when you have read our newsletter and whether you have clicked any links contained therein. In addition to further technical data, such as data about your computer hardware and your IP address, the data processed will be stored so that we can optimize our newsletter and respond to the wishes of our readers. The data will therefore increase the quality and attractiveness of our newsletter.

The legal basis for sending the newsletter and the analysis is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a) GDPR.

You may revoke your prior consent to receive this newsletter under Art. 7 Para. 3 GDPR with future effect. All you have to do is inform us that you are revoking your consent or click on the unsubscribe link contained in each newsletter.

#### **CloudFlare**

To secure our website and to optimize loading times, we use the CloudFlare CDN (content delivery network). This is a service of Cloudflare Inc., 101 Townsend Street, San Francisco, California 94107, USA, hereinafter referred to as "CloudFlare".

Through certification according to the EU-US Privacy Shield

([https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000GnZKAA0&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000GnZKAA0&status=Active))

CloudFlare guarantees that it will follow the EU's data protection regulations when processing data in the United States.

The legal basis for collecting and processing this information is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in the secure operation of our website and in its optimization.

If you access our website, your queries are forwarded to CloudFlare servers. Statistical access data about your visit to our website is collected and CloudFlare stores a cookie on your terminal device via your browser. Access data includes

\- your IP address;

\- the page(s) on our site that you access;

\- type and version of internet browser you are using;

\- your operating system;

\- the website from which you came prior to visiting our website (referrer URL);

\- your length of stay on our site; and 

\- the frequency with which our pages are accessed.

The data is used by CloudFlare for statistical evaluations of the accesses as well as for the security and optimization of the offer.

If you do not agree to this processing, you have the option of preventing the installation of cookies by making the appropriate settings in your browser. Further details can be found in the section about cookies above.

CloudFlare offers further information about its data collection and processing as well your rights and your options for protecting your privacy at this link:

<https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/>.

#### **Google AdWords with Conversion Tracking**

Our website uses Google AdWords and conversion tracking. This is a service provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 (hereinafter: Google).

Through certification according to the EU-US Privacy Shield

[https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active)

Google guarantees that it will follow the EU's data protection regulations when processing data in the United States.

We use conversion tracking to provide targeted promotion of our site. The legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in the analysis, optimization, and economic operation of our site.

If you click on an ad placed by Google, the conversion tracking we use stores a cookie on your device. These so-called conversion cookies expire after 30 days and do not otherwise identify you personally.

If the cookie is still valid and you visit a specific page of our website, both we and Google can evaluate that you clicked on one of our ads placed on Google and that you were then forwarded to our website.

The data collected in this way is in turn used by Google to provide us with an evaluation of visits to our website and what visitors do once there. In addition, we receive information about the number of users who clicked on our advertisement(s) as well as about the pages on our site that are subsequently visited. Neither we nor third parties who also use Google AdWords will be able to identify you from this conversion tracking.

You can also prevent or restrict the installation of cookies by making the appropriate settings in your browser. Likewise, you can use the browser to delete cookies that have already been stored. However, the steps and measures required vary, depending on the browser you use. If you have any questions, please use the help function or consult the documentation for your browser or contact its maker for support.

In addition, Google provides further information with regard to its data protection practices at

<https://services.google.com/sitestats/de.html>

<http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>

<http://www.google.de/policies/privacy/>

in particular information on how you can prevent the use of your data.

#### **Google Remarketing**

We use the remarketing function on our website. This is a service provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 (hereinafter: Google).

Through certification according to the EU-US Privacy Shield

[https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active)

Google guarantees that it will follow the EU's data protection regulations when processing data in the United States.

We use this feature to deliver interest-based, personalized advertising on third-party websites that also participate in Google's advertising network.

The legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in the analysis, optimization, and economic operation of our site.

To allow this advertising service to function, Google stores a cookie with a sequence of numbers on your device via your browser when you visit our website. This cookie records both your visit and the use of our website in anonymous form. However, personal data will not be passed on. If you subsequently visit a third-party website that also uses the Google advertising network, advertising may appear that refers to our website or our offers there.

To permanently disable this feature, Google provides a browser plugin for most common browsers at

Likewise, the use of cookies from certain providers, e.g. via

or

<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>

can be deactivated by opt-out.

**Cross-device marketing** allows Google to track your usage patterns across multiple devices, so you may see interest-based, personalized advertising even when you switch devices. However, this requires that you have agreed to link your browsing history to your existing Google account.

Google offers more information about Google Remarketing at

<http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/>

#### **Microsoft Bing Ads**

Our website uses Bing Ads for remarketing and follow-up. This is a service of Microsoft Corporation, One Microsoft Way, Redmond, WA 98052 - 6399, USA, hereinafter referred to as "Microsoft", based on so-called Universal Event Tracking (UEN).

Through certification according to the EU-US Privacy Shield

([https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000KzNaAAK&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000KzNaAAK&status=Active))

Microsoft guarantees that it will follow the EU's data protection regulations when processing data in the United States.

The legal basis for collecting and processing this information is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in the analysis, optimization, and economic operation of our site.

If you click on an advertisement placed by us on the Bing search engine, Microsoft stores a cookie on your terminal device to track your activity via your browser. This cookie expires after 180 days and is not used for personal identification. If you visit certain pages of our website and the cookie has not yet expired, both Microsoft and we may recognize that you have clicked on an advertisement placed by us at Bing and have been forwarded to our website from there.

Microsoft uses the information collected by the tracking cookie to compile visit statistics for us. This provides us with information on the number of hits triggered by the advertising placed on Bing and which pages on our site were subsequently accessed. However, we do not receive any information that could be used to identify you personally.

In addition, Microsoft may be able to track your user behavior across multiple devices using cross-device tracking. This enables Microsoft to display personalized advertising across all devices.

If you do not agree to this processing, you have the option of preventing the installation of cookies by making the appropriate settings in your browser. Further details can be found in the section about cookies above.

If you have a Microsoft account, you can also change the settings for personalized advertising there at[ http://choice.microsoft.com/de-de/opt-out](http://choice.microsoft.com/de-de/opt-out).

Microsoft also provides additional information about Bing Ads, the collection and use of data, and your rights and disclosures about how you can protect your privacy at[ https://help.bingads.microsoft.com/#apex/3/de/53056/2](https://help.bingads.microsoft.com/#apex/3/de/53056/2) and[ https://privacy.microsoft.com/de-de/privacystatement](https://privacy.microsoft.com/de-de/privacystatement).

#### **Newsletter via WhatsApp**

You can also receive our free newsletter via the instant messaging service WhatsApp. WhatsApp is a service of WhatsApp Ireland Limited, 4 Grand Canal Square, Grand Canal Harbour, Dublin 2, Ireland, a subsidiary of WhatsApp Inc, 1601 Willow Road, Menlo Park, California 94025, USA, both hereinafter referred to as "WhatsApp". Some of the user data is processed on WhatsApp servers in the USA, which is certified according to the EU-US Privacy Shield.

[https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000TSnwAAG&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000TSnwAAG&status=Active)

WhatsApp guarantees that it will follow the EU's data protection regulations when processing data in the United States. In addition, WhatApp offers further information about its data protection practices at

<https://www.whatsapp.com/legal/#privacy-policy>

To receive our newsletter via WhatsApp, you need a WhatsApp account. Details of what information WhatsApp collects when you register can be found in WhatsApp's privacy policy.

If you then subscribe to our WhatsApp newsletter, the mobile number you entered during the subscription process will be processed by WhatsApp. In addition, your IP address and the date and time of your registration will be saved. During the registration process, your consent to receive this newsletter will be obtained together with a concrete description of the type of content it will offer and reference made to this privacy policy.

The legal basis for sending the newsletter and the analysis is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a) GDPR.

You may revoke your prior consent to receive this newsletter under Art. 7 Para. 3 GDPR with future effect. All you have to do is inform us that you are revoking your consent. You can also block newsletter delivery by changing the settings in the WhatsApp software on your device.

## **IV. Other**

### **How We Use the Information**

We use data to verify your identity, communicate with you about bUnited and our activities, contact you with marketing communications, and, in general, to operate, evaluate, and improve our performance. We also use the information to build higher quality, more useful services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our users regarding specific areas of our Site.

We may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information publicly, with our partners or with third parties. For example, we may share information to show trends about the general use of our site.

### **Children's Privacy**

The Site is not structured to attract children and no part of the Site is directed to persons under 13 years of age. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect personal information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access this Site in any manner.

### **Links to Other Sites**

Our Site may contain links to other sites. Other sites may also reference or link to our site. bUnited is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites.

We may disclose information you submitted via the Site and its services if we are required to do so by law, regulation, legal process or governmental request.

### **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

From time to time, we may change this privacy policy to accommodate new technologies, industry practices, regulatory requirements or for other purposes. We will provide notice to you if these changes are material and, where required by applicable law, we will obtain your consent. Notice may be by email to you at the last email address you provided us, by posting notice of such changes on our sites and applications, or by other means, consistent with applicable law.

### **Your Consent**

You consent to the data collection, use, disclosure and storage practices described in this privacy policy when you use any of our Services (as described below), including when you access any content or videos.
